BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.551114: Autokraft Box Corporation and Upholsterers' International Union of North America Local 465, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Code no.551335: Star Hat and Cap Company and United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union Local 5, 1964- 1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Code no.551424: Jervis Corporation and UAW Local 356, 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Code no.551569: Aetna Steel Products Corporation and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 2131, 1965- 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Code no.551599: Planters Peanuts Division of Standard Brands Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union Local 158, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Code no.551920: Connecticut Railway Lighting Company and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Code no.552129: Alton Box Board Company and Production, Merchandising and Distribution Employees Union Local 210, 1964- 1972 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Code no.552141: Simmons Machine Tool Corp. and Federal Labor Union, 23981, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Code no.552229: Potomac Sand and Gravel Company and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 77, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Code no.552267: Minneapolis Paper Merchants and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders Local 12, 1966-1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Code no.552305: American Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 5-434, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Code no.560002: League of NY Theatres, Inc. and Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1962-1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Code no.560016: Aerojet-General Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 749, 1965- 1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Code no.560193: Dexter Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Code no.560293: Wholesale Bakery Operators of Quincy and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union Local 203, 1965- 1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Code no.560457: Central Vermont Public Service Corporation and United Mine Workers of America Local 12747, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Code no.560457: Central Vermont Public Service Corporation and U.M.W.A. Local 12747, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Code no.560484: Boston Herald-Traveler Corporation and Newspaper Guild of Greater Boston, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Code no.560505: Ozark-Mahoning Co. and IAM Lodge 1846, 1966-1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Code no.560576: R. Hoe and Co. and Architectural and Engineering Guild Local 66, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Code no.560577: R. Hoe and Co. and International Molders' and Allied Workers' Union Local 305, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Code no.560609: Detroit Hotel Association and Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union Local 129, 1965- 1973 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Code no.560730: United Wholesale Grocery Co. and Michigan Conference of Teamsters Local 20, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Code no.560762: Contractors of Taunton, Mass. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 1035, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Code no.560777: Marchant Electronics and IAM Local 115, 1965-1971 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Code no.560828: APCO Mossberg Company and IAM Local 1359, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Code no.560952: General Dynamics Corporation and IBEW Local 116, 1966-1975 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Code no.561065: West Virginia Pulp and Paper and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 179, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Code no.561164: Florida West Coast Chapter of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Laborers International Union of North America Local 1207, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Code no.561209: Lone Star Gas Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 4-478, 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Code no.561212: Creative Buildings, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 44, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Code no.561238: Humble Oil and Refining Company and Clerical, Laboratory and Other Salary Employees, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Code no.561238: Standard Refinery Union, Inc. and Clerical, Laboratory and Other Salary Employees, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Code no.561253: Smith-Lee Co. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 53, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Code no.561309: Manufacturers of Illumination Products, Inc. and IBEW Local 3, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Code no.561344: Mobil Oil Corporation and Associated Petroleum Employees Union, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Code no.561391: Formed Tubes, Inc. and UAW Local 873, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Code no.561516: Rolled Plate Metal Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 5693, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Code no.561517: Curtiss-Wright Corporation and Aircraft Lodge Local 703, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Code no.561543: Stephen Leedom Carpet Co., Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America Local 80, 1965-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Code no.561571: Union Starch and Refining Company, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-663, 1964- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Code no.561572: General Dynamics/Fort Worth Division and IAM Local 776, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Code no.561590: Weaver Division, Dura Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Local 1522, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Code no.561601: Blackwell Zinc. Co. Inc. and Smelter Workers Union Local 21538, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Code no.561610: Northern States Power Company and IBEW Local 928, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Code no.561517: Gar Wood Industries, Inc. and IAM Local 1194, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Code no.561648: Lear Siegler, Inc., Olympic Radio and Television Division and IBEW Local 1010, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Code no.561692: H.K. Porter Company, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aero Space Workers, Lodge 1827, 1966- 1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Code no.561693: H.K. Porter Company, Inc., Quaker Works and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 63, 1967- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Code no.561703: Rockland Webbing Company and United Textile Workers of America Local 310, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Code no.561832: Aero-Corry Division and IAM Lodge 1508, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Code no.561856: Wellman Dynamics Corporation and UAW Local 804, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Code no.561873: Philadelphia Lager Beer Brewers' Association and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers Locals 5, 183, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Code no.561919: North American Rockwell Corporation, Columbus Division and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 124, 1965- 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Code no.570020: General Refractories Company and United Brick and Clay Workers of America Local 763, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Code no.570065: Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts, Inc. and Carpenters Local 762 of Quincy, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Code no.570075: Black, Sivalls and Bryson, Inc., Oklahoma City Fabricating Plant and United Steelworkers of America Local 2098, 1966- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Code no.570083: Frontier Industries, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Code no.570225: Bedding Manufacturers' Association of Philadelphia and Upholsterers' International Union of North America Local 404, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Code no.570270: St. Louis County Water Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 448, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Code no.570363: Shell Chemical Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union, 1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Code no.570369: Tacoma Area Boom Operators and International Woodworkers of America Local 3-129, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Code no.570410: Magnus Metal Division of National Lead Company and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Local 758, 1966-1962 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Code no.570420: San Francisco Beauty Shops and Journeymen Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists and Proprietors International Union of America Local 148, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Code no.570426: Schenley Industries, Inc. and United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Code no.570443: A.B. and W. Transit Co. and Amalgamated Transit Union Local 1131, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Code no.570458: McGraw-Edison Company, Edison Voicewriter Division and IUE Local 467, 1969-1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Code no.570557: Professional Laundry Institute of Chicagoland and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 399, 1966- 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Code no.570590: Imperial Tobacco Group, Ltd. and Tobacco Workers International Union Local 278, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Code no.570602: Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Union Local 338, 1965-1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Code no.570637: Phillips Petroleum Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 5-232, 1964-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Code no.570674: American Zinc Company of Illinois and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-347, 1966- 1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Code no.570684: Zia Company and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry Local 412, 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Code no.570703: Lima Area Contractors Association and North Central Ohio District Council of Carpenters Locals 373, 976, 796, 1287, 1967- 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Code no.570706: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Grocery and Food Warehousemen Local 635, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Code no.570823: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 2471, 1966- 1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Code no.570857: Fairchild Hiller, Aircraft Division and UAW Local 842, 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Code no.570872: Joy Manufacturing Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Code no.570923: Howard Foundry Company and IAM District 8, 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Code no.570959: Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Independent Union of Plant Protection Employees Local 14, 1967- 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Code no.571205: W and G Sewing Equipment Company and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 72, 1967- 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Code no.580015: Standard Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers' International Union Local 7-395, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Code no.580031: Associated General Contractors of America, Cincinnati Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers Locals 18, 18A, 18B, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Code no.580056: New England Road Builders Association, Inc. and Hoisting and Portable Engineers Local Union 478, 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Code no.580067: Sherwin-Williams Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-230, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Code no.580113: I.B. Kleinert Rubber Company and American Federation of Rubber Workers Local 20499, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Code no.580116: Beaunit Fibers and United Textile Workers of America Local 201, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Code no.580117: Ready Mixed and Aggregate Industry Employers and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 17, 17A, 17B, 1963- 1975 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Code no.580152: Arkansas Printing and Lithographing Co. of Little Rock and Little Rock Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union Local 59, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Code no.580198: Security-Columbian Banknote Company and Steel and Copper Plate Engravers Local 25, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Code no.590001: Del Monte Corporation and IAM Lodge 1663, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Code no.590024: Tecumseh Products, Marion, Ohio Division and UAW Local 750, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Code no.590033: Reichart Furniture Company and Independent Furniture Workers of Ohio Valley, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Code no.590060: Atlantic Coast Engraving Company and Lithographers and Photo Engravers International Local 218, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Code no.590060: Aslinger Engraving Co. and Lithographers and Photo Engravers International Local 218, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Code no.590095: Clifton Manufacturing Company and Textile Workers Union of America Local 325, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Code no.590114: Labor Relations Division, Alabama Branch, AGC and Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons International Association Locals 62 and 695, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Code no.590133: National Tea Company and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America Local 2, 1968- 1971 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Code no.590142: Copperweld Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Code no.590144: Kaiser Steel Corporation and Northern California District Council of Laborers Local 371, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Code no.590146: Kaiser Steel Corporation and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 3, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Code no.590171: Government Services, Inc. and Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Local 639, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Code no.590175: Sperry Rand Corporation, Univac Division and Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Local 46, 1969- 1972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Code no.590176: Sperry Rand Corporation, Univac Division and Mohawk Valley Tool and Model Makers, Lodge 306 of District Lodge 157, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Code no.590180: Associated Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 24, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Code no.590198: Ritter Company and Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers Local 113, 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Code no.590274: Ivon R. Ford, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1561, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Code no.590275: Fred Sanders Corporation and United Distributive Workers, Council 30, 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Code no.590324: Thurston County Retail Drug Establishments and Retail Store Employees Union Local 367, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Code no.590356: Guerdon Industries, Inc. and UAW Local 1453, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Code no.590395: American Nurses' Association and Community and Social Agency Employees Local 1707, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Code no.590441: Westprint, Inc. and Employer and Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union Local 609, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Code no.590451: Magnavox Company of Tennessee and IAM Local 431, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Code no.590483: Kitchens of Sara Lee, Inc. and Bakery, Cracker, Pie, Yeast Drivers Union Local 734, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Code no.590506: U.S. Plywood-Champion Papers, Inc. and Industrial Workers of America Local 3-140, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Code no.590518: Michigan Memorial Institute and Service Employees' International Union Local 79, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Code no.590518: Franklin Medical Institute and Service Employees' International Union Local 79, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Code no.590535: North Texas Contractors Association and Masons and Plasterers' International Union of America Local 5, 1970- 1973 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Code no.590544: Good Humor Corporation and Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union Local 757, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Code no.590600: Northwest Paper Company and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 318, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Code no.590600: Potlatch Forests, Inc. and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 318, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Code no.590650: Associated General Contractors of America and Plasterers and Cement Masons District Council Locals 68, 252, 505, 1966- 1972 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Code no.590652: Tile and Marble Contractors of South Bend, Indiana and Bricklayer's Union Local 18, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Code no.591084: Connecticut Construction Industries Association, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 478, 1972- 1973 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Code no.590324: Retail Drug Establishments of Thurston County, Waashington, and Retail Clerks International, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Thurston County Retail Drug Establishments and Retail Store Employees Union Local 367, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Agreement effective 06/01/1969 and expires on 06/01/1972. Covers 50 workers in Thurston, WA.
    Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
  - Item 2: Thurston County Retail Drug Establishments and Retail Store Employees Union Local 367, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Agreement effective 06/01/1972 and expires on 06/01/1973. Covers 40 workers in Thurston, WA.
- Code no.590544: Good Humor Corporation and Teamsters, 1970-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Good Humor Corporation and Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union Local 757, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1970 and expires on 04/30/1972. Covers 600 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.
  - Item 2: Good Humor Corporation and Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union Local 757, 1972-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1972 and expires on 04/30/1975. Covers 600 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.